WELL, THAT THING'S
CLEARLY IN THE WAY.
ALL RIGHT. AHA!
( electrical buzzing)
( screams )
DAMN FRIDGE!
HEY, JOEY, HOW YOU DOING?
GREAT...
ROOMIE.
HUH. YEAH, I GUESS
WE ARE ROOMMATES NOW.
NOW THAT
YOU BRING IT UP
UH, OUR FRIDGE IS BROKEN.
WE HAVE TO GET A NEW ONE.
I CHECKED AROUND AND
YOUR HALF IS $400.
THANKS A LOT, RACH.
I'M NOT PAYING
FOR HALF OF THAT.
I'M ONLY STAYING HERE
UNTIL MY APARTMENT GETS FIXED.
LOOK, RACH, MY PARENTS
BOUGHT THIS FRIDGE
JUST AFTER I WAS BORN, OKAY?
NOW, I HAVE NEVER
HAD A PROBLEM WITH IT.
THEN YOU SHOW UP
AND IT BREAKS.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL YOU?
THAT REFRIGERATORS
DON'T LIVE AS LONG AS PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT, NOW,
YOU KNOW THAT THE A.T.M.
WILL ONLY LET YOU
TAKE OUT $300 AT A TIME
SO I'LL TAKE A CHECK
FOR THE OTHER $100.
YOU'RE JOKING, RIGHT?
OF COURSE I'M JOKING.
I DON'T TAKE CHECKS.
THANK GOD YOU'RE PRETTY.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU
LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN
YOUR DAY, YOUR WEEK ♪
♪ YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
HEY.
HI.
DO YOU GUYS KNOW
ANY CUTE GUYS?
WELL, OF COURSE I DO.
MY GOOD FRIEND
JOEY OVER HERE.
OH, I'M SORRY.
THANK YOU, CHANDLER.
ANYWAY...
THERE'S THIS BIG CHARITY BALL
THIS WEEKEND
AND RALPH LAUREN BOUGHT A TABLE,
SO I KIND OF HAVE TO GO.
WHAT'S THE CHARITY?
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMETHING, EITHER TREES,
OR... DISEASE...
RALPH MUMBLES A LOT.
DOES RALPH MUMBLE WHEN
YOU'RE NOT PAYING ATTENTION?
YEAH, IT'S WEIRD.
BUT THE THING IS,
I NEED TO FIND A DATE.
WHAT KIND OF GUY
ARE YOU LOOKING FOR?
WELL, SOMEONE
THAT HAS HIS OWN TUX
OR THE ABILITY TO RENT A TUX.
SO HE HAS TO BE A MALE
WHO HAS AT LEAST $50.
OOH, SO CLOSE.
HEY, EVERYBODY.
HI.
HI THERE.
THIS IS ELIZABETH.
All:
HI.
I'M THE STUDENT.
OH, ISN'T SHE CUTE?
NO.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS PROBABLY
NONE OF MY BUSINESS
BUT WEREN'T YOU GUYS SUPPOSED TO
NOT BE SEEN IN PUBLIC TOGETHER?
OH, WE'RE NOT TOGETHER.
NO, WE'RE JUST TWO PEOPLE
WHO HAPPENED TO HAVE RUN
INTO EACH OTHER
HERE AT THE COFFEE HOUSE.
( giggling )
OH, SLY.
I REALLY WANTED TO
MEET YOU GUYS, BUT
I HAVE TO RUN.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER?
All:
OKAY.
BYE, ROSS.
BYE.
OOPS. DIDN'T MEAN TO RUN
INTO YOU LIKE THAT, SIR.
OH, THAT IS
QUITE ALL RIGHT, MA'AM.
BYE.
SO, WHY IS SHE LEAVING?
IS IT A SCHOOL NIGHT
AND SHE HAS A LOT
OF HOMEWORK TO DO?
YES, HER MOLECULAR EPIDEMIOLOGY
PAPER IS DUE TOMORROW.
OH, TELL HER GOOD LUCK
WITH THAT.
ANYONE ELSE? HUH?
BRING 'EM ON.
OH! WHEN'S HER BIRTHDAY?
I DON'T KNOW, RACHEL. WHY?
WELL, YOU KNOW,
IT'S JUST BEEN SO LONG
SINCE I'VE BEEN
TO CHUCK E. CHEESE.
( groans )
OH, I LIKE ELIZABETH.
WELL, THANKS.
YEAH, IN FACT, I
LIKE HER SO MUCH
THAT YOU TELL HER
I WANT MY COOKIES
EARLY THIS YEAR.
YOU KNOW...
A BOX OF THIN
MINTS AND SOME
TAGALONGS.
HEY, COME ON,
GIVE HIM A BREAK.
ROSS, SERIOUSLY,
HOW'S IT GOING WITH HER?
WELL, IT'S ACTUALLY BEEN GREAT.
SHE'S 20, SO SHE'S NOT LOOKING
FOR ANYTHING TOO SERIOUS
WHICH IS PERFECT FOR ME
RIGHT NOW.
WELL, THAT IS GREAT.
AND SERIOUSLY, SHE
SEEMS VERY NICE.
THANKS. I KNOW YOU GUYS LIKE
TO GIVE ME A HARD TIME AND ALL
BUT IT REALLY MEANS A LOT TO ME
THAT YOU LIKE HER.
JUST KNOWING THAT YOU GUYS
ARE LIKE...
OKAY, I GOT A GOOD ONE.
OKAY, UM...
WHAT IS SHE, LIKE, 12?
CHANDLER, DO YOU THINK
WE TALK ABOUT
OUR RELATIONSHIP ENOUGH?
YEAH.
DO WE HAVE ANY FRUIT ROLL-UPS?
HEY.
OKAY, I JUST THOUGHT OF
THE PERFECT GUY FOR RACHEL
TO TAKE TO HER THING.
OH, THAT'S SO FUNNY,
BECAUSE WE FOUND SOMEONE, TOO.
OH, THAT'S GOOD.
I GUESS SHE'LL HAVE A CHOICE
BETWEEN MY GUY AND YOUR WEIRDO.
WHY WOULD OUR GUY
BE A WEIRDO?
'CAUSE THAT'S JUST YOUR TASTE.
( fake laugh )
SEE, RACHEL'S NOT GOING
TO PICK YOUR STUPID GUY.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH.
MY GUY IS A LAWYER
WHO DOES VOLUNTEER WORK
AND HE HAS ONE OF THESE.
A FACE ASS?
A CHIN DIMPLE.
WELL, UH, YOU KNOW, OUR
GUY WORKS WITH CHANDLER
AND HE'S REALLY
NICE AND SMART
AND HE'S A GREAT DRESSER.
HAVE YOU SEEN YOUR GUY'S BODY?
NO. OUR GUY'S
JUST A FLOATING HEAD.
WELL, MY GUY
IS SPECTACULAR, OKAY?
HE'S A MASSAGE CLIENT.
AND ONE TIME,
WHEN HE WAS ON THE TABLE
I LOOKED AT IT,
AND I MEAN ALL OF IT.
YOU'RE NOT SUPPOSED TO LOOK.
OH, YEAH,
LIKE THERE ARE POLICE FOR THAT.
YOU LOOK? YOU-YOU MASSAGE ME.
I KNOW.
ALL RIGHT, FINE.
YOUR GUY MAY HAVE
A GREAT BODY
BUT OUR GUY IS
REALLY FUNNY.
CHANDLER FUNNY?
OUR GUY'S A GREAT DANCER.
MY GUY'S WELL-READ.
OUR GUY HAS GREAT HAIR.
MY GUY HAS GREAT TEETH.
OUR GUY SMELLS INCREDIBLE.
DO YOU WANT OUR GUY
TO BE YOUR GUY?
HEY.
UH...
WELL, YOU...
YOU DON'T LOOK GOOD, JOE.
WELL, THE FRIDGE BROKE
SO I HAD TO EAT EVERYTHING.
COLD CUTS, ICE CREAM, LIMES...
HEY, WHAT WAS IN THAT BROWN JAR?
THAT'S STILL IN THERE?
NOT ANYMORE.
SO, ANYWAY,
HOW DO YOU WANT TO PAY ME?
IS THIS A SERVICE
YOU'RE PROVIDING ME?
NO, NO, NO...
FOR MY NEW FRIDGE--
OUR NEW FRIDGE.
OUR NEW FRIDGE?
I DON'T LIVE HERE ANYMORE.
SO WHAT?
LOOK, OKAY, SUPPOSE WE WERE
A DIVORCED COUPLE.
UH-HUH.
AND I GOT CUSTODY
OF THE KID, RIGHT?
NOW, SUPPOSE THE KID DIES
AND I GOT TO BUY A NEW KID.
OKAY.
GIVE ME $400.
PROFESSOR GELLER?
MM? OH, A STUDENT
I DON'T KNOW.
I WAS WONDERING IF I COULD
TALK TO YOU FOR A MOMENT?
YES, OF COURSE.
WHAT WOULD THIS
BE REGARDING?
MAKING OUT IN YOUR OFFICE.
WH-- SHH...
OF-OF COURSE.
WHY DON'T WE GO INSIDE?
( giggles )
MM-MM...
OH, OH...
WHAT?
DOORKNOB.
SORRY.
UM, I ACTUALLY DO
NEED TO TALK TO YOU.
OH, OKAY, WHAT ABOUT?
SPRING VACATION.
YEAH, WE HAVE TIME OFF
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE
GOING ON TRIPS, AND...
PROFESSOR GELLER?
YES, PROFESSOR FRIE-SEN...
STIN-LINDER.
I'LL BE WITH YOU
IN ONE MOMENT.
SO, I WILL TAKE ONE BOX
OF THE THIN MINTS.
YOU DON'T UNDERSTAND.
ELIZABETH WAS ABOUT TO ASK ME
TO GO ON A TRIP WITH HER.
IS THAT TAKING IT SLOW?
I'M NOT READY
FOR THIS, OKAY?
WHAT DO I TELL HER?
JUST TELL HER THE TRUTH.
TELL HER
YOU'RE NOT READY.
I COULD DO THAT.
WHAT IF SHE GETS UPSET?
THEN YOU DISTRACT HER
WITH A BARBIE DOLL.
OR...
YOU COULD JUST, YOU KNOW...
WHAT THE HELL ARE YOU DOING?
WH...
WHAT THE HELL AM I DOING?
YOU JUST BROKE MY FRIDGE!
WHAT? HOW DO YOU KNOW IF...
HOW DO YOU KNOW
IT'S EVEN BROKEN?
OH, YOU THINK I DON'T KNOW
WHAT BREAKS MY FRIDGE?
EXCUSE ME.
WELL, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
BROKEN.
THAT'LL BE $400.
JOEY, I SAW YOU PUSH HIM.
YOU PUSHED HIM.
JOEY, I DID NOT
BREAK THIS, OKAY?
THAT HAS BEEN BROKEN
FOR A WHILE.
CHANDLER, REMEMBER I TOLD YOU
ABOUT OUR FRIDGE?
UH-HUH.
I STILL HAVEN'T GOTTEN
THE CHECK FOR
YOUR HALF YET.
DO NOT GIVE
HIM ANY MONEY.
I'M NOT TALKING TO YOU!
YOU BROKE MY FRIDGE!
YOU WANTED TO SEE ME,
PROFESSOR GELLER?
YES. YES, PLEASE COME IN.
OOH-OOH...
DOORKNOB?
YEAH, IT KIND OF
GROWS ON YOU.
( chuckling )
ACTUALLY, I WANTED TO FINISH
TALKING TO YOU
ABOUT SPRING VACATION.
OH, GOOD.
LOOK, I...
LOOK, I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME
WITH YOU
AND I JUST DON'T WANT US
TO MOVE TOO FAST
OR PUT TOO MUCH PRESSURE ON US.
SO, I'M SORRY.
I JUST DON'T THINK
WE SHOULD GO AWAY TOGETHER YET.
IT'S TOO SOON.
UM, ROSS, I THINK YOU
MISUNDERSTOOD
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
I JUST WANTED TO TELL YOU
THAT I'M GOING TO FLORIDA
FOR A COUPLE OF WEEKS.
NO. I THINK YOU MISUNDERSTOOD
WHAT I WAS SAYING.
WHAT I MEANT WAS...
YOU ARE SO ADORABLE.
THAT... LET'S TALK ABOUT THAT.
( giggles )
HI.
HEY.
HOW DID IT GO
WITH ELIZABETH?
OH, OH, IT WAS FINE.
UH, IT WAS JUST
A MISUNDERSTANDING.
SHE DIDN'T WANT ME
TO GO WITH HER.
SHE JUST WANTED TO LET ME KNOW
THAT SHE'S GOING TO FLORIDA
FOR SPRING VACATION.
WAIT A MINUTE.
IS SHE GOING FOR SPRING VACATION
OR IS SHE GOING FOR
SPRING BREAK? WHOO-HOO!
WHAT'S-WHAT'S THE DIFFERENCE?
WELL, A SPRING VACATION
YOU'RE DOING NICE THINGS
WITH YOUR GRANDPARENTS.
SPRING BREAK,
YOU'RE DOING FRAT GUYS.
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT?
NOT ALL SPRING BREAKS
ARE LIKE THAT.
WHAT'D YOU DO ON YOURS?
I WENT TO EGYPT WITH MY DAD.
I CAN SEE IT NOW.
LOOK, DAD, IT'S THE SPHINX.
WHOO-WHOO!
I THINK ELIZABETH
IS A LITTLE MORE SERIOUS
THAN SPRING BREAK... WHOO-HOO!
ALL RIGHT, I MEAN, COME ON.
SHE'S TAKING MY CLASS.
AND SLEPT
WITH THE PROFESSOR.
I'M GOING TO CALL HER.
YEAH.
HEY.
YOU GUYS, UM, I WANT YOU
TO MEET SEBASTIAN.
HI.
WE JUST MET AT THE NEWSSTAND.
WE BOTH GRABBED FOR THE LAST
FIELD AND STREAM.
WHAT? I READ THAT.
CAN I GET YOU
A CUP OF COFFEE?
OH, YES, THANK YOU.
RACHEL, WHAT THE HELL IS THIS?
WHAT?
YOU ASKED US TO FIND YOU A GUY
AND THEN YOU COME TRAIPSING
IN HERE WITH A GUY OF YOUR OWN?
YOU FOUND ME A GUY?
YES, WE FOUND YOU
A REALLY CUTE
AND FUNNY GUY
FROM CHANDLER'S WORK.
YEAH, AND I FOUND YOU ONE, TOO
WHO IS NOT A WEIRDO.
WELL, YOU KNOW WHAT,
THOUGH, YOU GUYS?
I REALLY APPRECIATE THAT
BUT I'M JUST GOING TO TAKE
SEBASTIAN TO THE CHARITY.
ARE YOU SURE?
BECAUSE OUR GUY
SMELLS INCREDIBLE.
WOULD YOU STOP IT
WITH THAT ALREADY?
HERE YOU GO.
OH, THANK YOU.
SURE.
SO, SEBASTIAN
DO YOU DO ANY VOLUNTEER WORK?
UH, NO, NOT REALLY. WHY?
NO REASON; IT'S JUST
I KNOW A SINGLE GUY
WHO DOES CARE
ABOUT OTHER PEOPLE.
ARE YOU FUNNY?
EXCUSE ME?
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
ARE YOU FUNNY?
TELL US A JOKE.
LOOK, I JUST WANTED TO
HAVE COFFEE WITH RACHEL.
YEAH, WELL,
SO DO A LOT OF PEOPLE.
ACTUALLY, UH, I
GOT TO GET GOING.
OH...
GIVE ME A CALL
SOMETIME.
YOU DIDN'T GIVE ME
YOUR PHONE NUMBER.
OKAY, SEE YOU LATER.
TURNS OUT HE IS
KIND OF FUNNY.
I CANNOT BELIEVE YOU GUYS.
HE WAS REALLY NICE
AND HE JUST LEFT
BECAUSE OF YOU.
YEAH, BUT, SEBASTIAN?
WHAT IS THAT,
A CAT'S NAME?
Phoebe:
YEAH, YOU KNOW WHAT
I NOTICED, RACHEL?
HE SCARES EASY, YOU KNOW.
IS THAT THE KIND OF GUY
YOU WANT TO TAKE TO A BALL?
"HEY, SEBASTIAN, WOULD YOU
LIKE TO DANCE?"
"UH... OKAY, I GOT TO GO."
ALL RIGHT, GUYS,
STOP IT.
RACHEL, WE'RE VERY SORRY.
THAT WAS A VERY INSENSITIVE
THING FOR US TO DO
AND, YOU KNOW WHAT,
LET US MAKE IT UP TO YOU.
WE HAVE TWO REALLY
GREAT GUYS FOR YOU.
Phoebe:
YEAH, WHAT HAVE
YOU GOT TO LOSE?
YOU MIGHT EVEN END UP
WITH SOMEONE REALLY SPECIAL
IF YOU PICK MINE.
ALL RIGHT.
OKAY, SO YOU WILL
MEET OUR GUYS?
YES, I'LL MEET THEM.
IT DOESN'T MATTER
WHICH ONE YOU CHOOSE.
IT'S COMPLETELY UP TO YOU.
OUR GUY IS PERFECT...
OR YOU COULD GO OUT
WITH THE GUY
PHOEBE DEEMED NOT GOOD ENOUGH
TO GO OUT WITH HERSELF.
PHOEBE, THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY, YOU BROKE MY FRIDGE.
YOU OWE ME 400 BUCKS.
OKAY, SURE.
REALLY?
YEAH, YEAH.
OOH, TECHNICALLY,
YOU OWE ME $600
FOR SENDING OUT HAPPY THOUGHTS
ON YOUR LAST TEN AUDITIONS.
CALL IT EVEN?
OKAY.
WELL, THERE
YOU ARE.
SO WHAT DID ELIZABETH SAY?
WELL, IT TURNS OUT SHE IS GOING
TO DAYTONA FOR SPRING BREAK...
WHOO-HOO.
THAT MEANS WET T-SHIRT CONTESTS
GUYS DOING SHOTS
OFF OF GIRLS' BODIES
WAKING UP NEXT TO PEOPLE
YOU DON'T EVEN KNOW.
MAN, SHE IS GOING
TO HAVE A GREAT TIME.
IS SHE STAYING AT
THE HOTEL CORONA?
YOU KNOW THE HOTELS?
SURE. I WAS THERE.
SPRING BREAK '81. WHOO!
IN 1981, YOU WERE 13.
SO WHAT?
I DROVE DOWN,
SOLD T-SHIRTS.
HAD A BLAST.
AND YOU KNOW WHO
KNOWS HOW TO PARTY?
DRUNK COLLEGE CHICKS.
OKAY, SHE CAN'T GO.
ROSS, YOU CAN'T TELL HER
NOT TO GO.
YOU JUST STARTED DATING.
WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO DO?
NOTHING. YOU JUST HAVE
TO BE COOL WITH IT.
WELL, WHAT IF
SHE GOES DOWN THERE
AND SLEEPS WITH A BUNCH OF GUYS?
WELL, MAYBE YOU
DON'T MARRY THIS ONE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU'RE
GOING ON THIS TRIP.
YEAH, I'VE BEEN WORKING
SO HARD THIS SEMESTER.
I REALLY NEED TO GO
CRAZY, YOU KNOW?
BLOW OFF SOME STEAM.
SURE, SURE.
LOOK, I DON'T KNOW
IF YOUR PLANS ARE
FINALIZED YET, BUT...
HEY, I KNOW ANOTHER GREAT
WAY TO BLOW OFF STEAM.
WHAT?
ARE YOU INTO CRAFTS AT ALL?
ROSS, ARE YOU OKAY?
YEAH, OF COURSE... I'M OKAY.
I'M JUST BEING...
SUPPORTIVE.
SUPPORTIVE OF YOU
AND THIS WHOLE TRIP, AND...
WHAT-WHAT IS... WHAT'S THIS?
IT'S A BATHING SUIT.
TO WEAR IN FRONT OF PEOPLE?
IS THAT SUPPORTIVE?
IS THIS?
HEY.
WE'RE REALLY GLAD
YOU DECIDED TO
MEET OUR GUY.
YOU'RE GOING
TO LIKE HIM SO MUCH.
WHEN DO YOU WANT
TO MEET HIM?
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T WORK LATE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
TOMORROW NIGHT IS GOOD.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
WHY PUT OFF SOMETHING
TILL TOMORROW
YOU COULD DO RIGHT NOW?
ELDAD, COME HERE.
ELDAD,
THIS IS RACHEL.
HOW ARE YOU?
WELL, A LITTLE BLINDSIDED
BUT, YOU KNOW, GOOD.
ELDAD, SIT DOWN.
MOVE OVER.
MOVE OVER NOW.
THERE YOU GO.
THERE YOU ARE.
OKAY, OKAY,
WE CAN TAKE A HINT.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HERE?
THIS IS PATRICK.
HI.
OKAY, YOU'RE
TOO LATE, OKAY
BECAUSE SHE'S
ALREADY WITH OUR GUY.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU'RE RIGHT.
I AM TOO LATE.
THEY'RE SITTING
ON THE COUCH
AND TALKING.
COME ON.
RACHEL.
YEAH?
THIS IS PATRICK.
OH, HI.
THIS IS THE GUY
I WAS TELLING YOU ABOUT.
AND BELIEVE ME, THIS SUIT
DOES NOT DO JUSTICE
TO WHAT'S UNDERNEATH IT.
OKAY...
BUT, PHEEBS...
I'M JUST SORT OF IN
THE MIDDLE OF SOMETHING.
OH, OKAY, YEAH,
THAT'S OKAY.
HAVE A SEAT.
YOU CAN'T
DO THAT.
MAYBE I
SHOULD GO.
SIT DOWN.
WE'RE WINNING.
OKAY, YOU KNOW WHAT,
MAYBE I SHOULD GO.
NO! NO!
YOU HAVE A SEAT.
RACHEL, RACHEL, YOU
HAVEN'T TOUCHED
ELDAD'S HAIR.
IT IS THE SOFTEST HAIR.
I'M GOOD.
RACHEL, PATRICK IS REALLY RICH.
GIVE HER SOME MONEY.
WHAT?
UH... YOU KNOW
WHAT, PHOEBE.
THIS ISN'T REALLY WORTH
THE FREE MASSAGE.
THAT'S RIGHT, PATRICK.
BYE-BYE.
ELDAD IS MUCH MORE
COOPERATIVE
AND HE CAN DANCE.
YOU DANCE FOR RACHEL.
OH, MY GOD...
NO, NO, NO,
DON'T DANCE FOR ME!
PLEASE, DON'T DANCE.
WHAT IS THE MATTER
WITH YOU GUYS?
YEAH, OKAY, LET'S
TALK IT OUT.
AM I THE ONLY ONE THAT
THIS IS EMBARRASSING FOR?
I'M EMBARRASSED.
SHH, SHH, SHH.
I'LL TELL YOU
WHO SHOULD BE EMBARRASSED--
IT'S YOU GUYS.
COME ON, THIS
IS RIDICULOUS.
THANK YOU, BUT I DO NOT NEED
YOU TO GET ME A DATE.
THEN WHY DID
SHE ASK US...?
I AM STILL TALKING!
AND THEN YOU CHASE
AWAY THE ONE GUY
THAT I ACTUALLY LIKED.
I MEAN, NO OFFENSE
TO YOU GUYS, REALLY.
I MEAN, CONGRATULATIONS
ON... ALL THE CASH.
AND... AND...
YOU KNOW, YOU REALLY
WOW, YOU DO HAVE
VERY SOFT HAIR.
BUT I WOULD MUCH RATHER
GO TO THE BALL ALL BY MYSELF
THAN GO THROUGH
ANY MORE OF THIS.
GOOD-BYE.
NOW, DO YOU USE SOME SORT
OF SPECIAL CONDITIONER
ON THAT HAIR?
YES, PAPAYA EXTRACT.
THANK YOU.
SO, UH, HAVE
A GREAT TIME
DOWN THERE.
I WILL.
DID YOU PACK
THAT BATHING SUIT?
YEAH.
IT WAS PRETTY FUNNY WHEN
I HID IT FOR A WHILE, HUH?
ANYWAY, UM...
I AM WORRIED ABOUT
THAT BATHING SUIT.
NOT BECAUSE
IT'S REVEALING
WHICH I'M FINE WITH.
NO, I'M CONCERNED
ABOUT YOUR HEALTH...
UM, SUN EXPOSURE.
OH, DON'T WORRY.
I HAVE PLENTY
OF SUNBLOCK.
IT'S SPF-30.
WELL, IF WHAT'S
IN THE BOTTLE
IS ACTUALLY 30.
I MEAN, SOMETIMES
YOU GET 30
SOMETIMES IT'S FOUR.
AND I SWEAR TO GOD
MORE OFTEN THAN NOT,
IT'S JUST MILK.
ROSS, IT'S GOING
TO BE OKAY.
I'M NOT GOING DOWN THERE
TO HOOK UP WITH
A BUNCH OF GUYS.
I REALLY LIKE YOU.
I LIKE HOW THINGS
ARE GOING BETWEEN US.
REALLY?
YEAH. I'M JUST GOING
DOWN THERE TO RELAX
AND HANG OUT
WITH MY FRIENDS.
OKAY. COOL.
OH, HEY,
HERE THEY ARE.
HEY, ELIZABETH!
( excited shouting )
CALL ME.
RACHEL, WE'RE SORRY
FOR PUSHING
THOSE GUYS ON YOU.
OH, THAT'S ALL RIGHT.
I ENDED UP HAVING
A REALLY GOOD TIME.
THE CHARITY WAS A BIG SUCCESS
AND THEY RAISED A LOT
OF MONEY AND AWARENESS.
SO WHAT WAS IT FOR, ANYWAY?
I WANT TO SAY A DISEASE.
HEY.
I GOT THIS REALLY WEIRD
MESSAGE FROM ROSS.
HE SAID TURN ON MTV.
ALL RIGHT.
OH, MY GOD! LOOK!
THAT'S ELIZABETH!
OH, OH,
PROFESSOR GELLER.
AH, TO BE 13 AGAIN.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]